davidicke.com 2017-06-24

# Privacy Policy | David Icke

POLICY ON PRIVACY, DATA, COOKIES AND MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS  
Data

We may ask you for certain information and you may submit personal data to all sites (such as your name, email address and contact details) when you subscribe or sign up to all sites.

We may also record which parts of all sites and services you are interested in as well as user traffic patterns and site use. This information will be kept securely in accordance with an internal security policy and may be used to:

(a) process your User Content, your subscription to all sites and to enable your use of all sites and associated services;  
(b) open and run your account and provide you with an up to date, efficient and reliable service;  
(c) generally run all sites;  
(d) send you marketing communications and newsletters when you sign up or subscribe to them.

By subscribing and submitting your data you agree to this use.

We will only use information collected about you in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

We will hold your personal data on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant activity.

We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.

If you believe we have information about you that you do not want us to have or that is incorrect please contact us as described below and we shall correct or remove the data as you reasonably request as soon as reasonably practicable.

Marketing Communications  
We give you a choice of whether or not you want us or other reputable companies to contact you about future events and new services or related activities that you may find useful. We will not sell or trade personal information to other companies but we would like to keep you informed of the developments on all sites and we would like to share data with other reputable companies who may have interesting offers and information for you (inside or outside the EU).

We will not send you any marketing emails or pass your information on to third parties unless you give your consent or you have given it already.

Cookies  
We use ‘cookies’ on all sites. Cookies are a way that information such as whether you have visited all sites before is recorded on your computer and used by us to improve all sites and the services available to you. If you do not wish for us to use cookies when you use all sites please adjust your Internet browser settings to not accept cookies. Your computer’s help file should tell you how to do this but please note that this may affect your ability to use all sites.

Since May 2011, the laws in the EU in respect of how website operators use cookies (and similar tools) has been updated by way of the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) (Amendment) Regulations 2011. The legislation requires website operators to acquire the pre-informed consent of visitors to a website before all non-essential cookies (and similar tools) are installed on the user’s hard drives. We are reviewing how the internet industry implements this legislation, however until such time as there is a unified position, then this Privacy Policy including Cookies Notice and your applicable browser settings shall be deemed your pre-informed consent to us using cookies (and other similar tools) on your visit to all sites. If you subsequently wish to revoke this consent, you may do so by deleting the cookies (and similar tools) via your browser tools settings. Please note that by deleting or blocking the use of cookies (or similar tools), you may not be able to access all parts of all sites, or it may detrimentally affect your user experience on all sites.

If you don’t disable cookies all sites will ask for and store details including your name and email address and may automatically insert certain information on the subscription or User Content forms so that you can use all sites with less form filling.

To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete then, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org.

Privacy  
If you have any other concerns over privacy, this privacy policy or all sites please contact webmaster@davidicke.com as described below.

CONTACT INFORMATION  
All questions, comments or enquiries for Davidicke.com should be directed:

By Post: Sean Adl-Tabatabai  
C/O Davidicke.com  
Suite 2, 185a High Street  
Ryde  
Isle of Wight  
PO33 2PN  
United Kingdom

By email to Sean Adl-Tabatabai at webmaster@davidicke.com

All questions, comments or enquiries for Davidickebooks.co.uk should be directed:

By Post: David Icke Books Ltd.  
Suite 2, 185a High Street  
Ryde  
Isle of Wight  
PO33 2PN  
United Kingdon

By email to David Icke Books Ltd at info@davidickebooks.co.uk
